<resources>
    <string name="app_name">PittAPI</string>
    <string name="title_activity_building__info">Building_Info</string>
    <string name="cathy_building_info">
        The Cathedral of Learning, otherwise known as the most beautiful building in the world, was built in the 1920\'s.
        Standing at 535 feet (163 m for those weird metric people), it is the tallest educational building in the Western Hemisphere,
        the second tallest university building in the world, and the second tallest gothic-styled building in the world. The Cathedral
        has 30 nationality rooms, 28 of which are used for classes. Each room was dedicated to a culture that influenced the growth of
        Pittsburgh at or around the time of the University's founding. According to audio experts, the main room of the Cathedral, known
        Common Room, reduces sound by using acoustical tiles as the stones between the ribs of vaulting. But if you were to ask any of the
        students, thats a load of mumbo jumbo.
    </string>
    <string name="sennott_building_info">
        Sennott Square, don\'t forget the two n\'s and t\'s, was built in the early 2000\'s and was the largest University of Pittsburgh
        building built since 1978. Quite the multipurpose building, Sennott contains 4 floors of offices and classrooms, large amounts of
        retail space, and both over and underground parking. It currently houses Pitt\'s College of Business Administration, Department of
        Psychology, and School of Computing and Information's Computer Science department. What many people don't know is that during
        Halloween time, it doubles as a scary maze! Participants are tasked with finding a classroom in the building while disgruntled
        students appear out of the depths of the mysterious networking lab. Only one person has successfully found their classroom since
        the mazes started in 2004.
    </string>
    <string name="hillman_building_info">
        Sennott Square, don\'t forget the two n\'s and t\'s, was built in the early 2000\'s and was the largest University of Pittsburgh
        building built since 1978. Quite the multipurpose building, Sennott contains 4 floors of offices and classrooms, large amounts of
        retail space, and both over and underground parking. It currently houses Pitt\'s College of Business Administration, Department of
        Psychology, and School of Computing and Information's Computer Science department. What many people don't know is that during
        Halloween time, it doubles as a scary maze! Participants are tasked with finding a classroom in the building while disgruntled
        students appear out of the depths of the mysterious networking lab. Only one person has successfully found their classroom since
        the mazes started in 2004.
    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_pitt_scores">PittScores</string>
    <string name="title_activity_BuildingTimes">BuildingTimes</string>
    <string name="title_activity_pitt_weather">PittWeather</string>
    <string name="sports_title"> Pitt Scores</string>
    <string name="vs"> vs. </string>
    <string name="building_title"> Building Hours </string>
    <string name="check_games">Check for Upcoming Games</string>
    <string name="continu">Continue to Next App</string>
    <string name="closed">--CLOSED--</string>
</resources>
